Marc Sánchez Marchador

The Hague, Netherlands

+34 652 622 525 | marc.snchez@gmail.com | LinkedIn: Marc Sánchez Marchador

Profile

I specialize in growth strategies, performance marketing, and product development. I have a 360-degree view of all the necessary actions and platforms to execute strategies, including CRM, affiliate, automation, email, paid media, content strategy, inbound, and others.

Education

ESERP Business & Law School

Degree in Marketing, Advertising and Public Relations.

Barcelona, Spain (2019 - 2023)

Professional Experience

Performance Marketing Specialist | Glovo App

I was responsible for creating and managing Google Ads campaigns to draw in and engage potential users. I was constantly optimizing these campaigns by analyzing Ad Group and Assets KPIs, as well as the overall campaign performance within the display network. To ensure the most accurate measurement of results, I conducted incrementality tests.

Barcelona, Spain (May 2023 - Nov 2023)

Product Marketing Manager (B2B SaaS) | Dost Al Solutions

Developed growth hacking and product-led growth strategies for a B2B startup. Managed content planning, graphic design, software UX design, and paid media campaigns on Google Ads and LinkedIn Ads. Additionally, this included email marketing and the integration of all channels with Hubspot as the main CRM. Also assisted the sales department with sequences and workflows.

Barcelona, Spain (Jan 2022 - May 2023)

Marketing Consultant | Arch Agency

I developed and implemented strategic marketing plans for clients, overseeing digital campaigns, content creation, analytics, and reporting. I also managed client relationships and pursued new business opportunities.

Barcelona, Spain (Sept 2021 - Mar 2022)

Senior Account Executive | MODO in Action

Development of digital strategies, use of communication channels, data and market analysis, use of Paid Media tools for promotional campaigns on Facebook Ads and Google Ads and development of strategies for clients in HubSpot.

Barcelona, Spain (Oct 2020 - Sept 2021)

Skills

- · Market Research: Identified market trends at Glovo, improving campaign strategies.
- Project Management: Coordinated cross-functional teams to launch Dost's go-to-market strategy.
- Data analytics: Utilized Tableau and mParticle for audience and budget projections at Glovo.
- Data-driven solutions: Extracted insights from complex data for decision making at Glovo, Dost and Arch.
- · Process automation: Used AI for automation and app leverage at Dost and MODO.
- Performance: Increased app users (Acquisition & Activation) through effective campaign management at Glovo, Dost and MODO.
- SEA: Managed 500k€ monthly ad spend, scaling Glovo's SEE region.

Languages

- · Native in written and spoken Spanish and Catalan
- Proficient in written and spoken English.

Other relevant information

- Have experience with emerging technologies such as Blockchain (DeFi protocols, smart contracts, blockchain security, and technical foundation) and Al (automation, app leverage, and APIs).
- · Completed an exchange year in Ireland, Galway.
- · Earned Google Marketing Certifications.